In this exercise, you'll be creating a NAT gateway and associating it with a subnet.
在此练习中 您将创建 NAT 网关并将其与子网相关联
In order to do that,
为了做到这一点
let's take a look at how you would create a NAT gateway.
让我们来看看您如何创建 NAT 网关
NAT gateways ask you for a couple of options,.
NAT 网关会询问您是否有几个选项
The first is the subnet.
第一个是子网
So you'll want to pick the subnet within
所以你要在
the new VPC that you just created, your public subnet.
您刚刚创建的新 VPC  即公共子网
The NAT gateway itself sits in a public subnet,
NAT 网关本身位于公共子网中
and then it has access to the Internet from there.
然后它就能从那里进入互联网
To pick your Elastic IP address,
要选择弹性 IP 地址
you can allocate a new IP address,
您可以分配新的 IP 地址
or if you already have one in your account you can use that,
或者你的账户里已经有一个你可以用这个
but this is the public address that the NAT gateway itself will use.
但这是 NAT 网关本身将使用的公共地址
Once you have your NAT gateway,
一旦有了 NAT 网关
you'll look at your routing tables,
你会看你的路由表
and you'll look for the routing table that does not have
你会去找那些没有
an explicit subnet association already.
显式子网关联
The one that does have the subnet association is the one that's already in use.
具有子网关联的是已在使用的子网关联
We take a look at this routing table and then the routes within it.
我们看看这个路由表 然后再看看其中的路由
We'll see that the only route is local route to the CDIR range of the VPC.
我们会看到 唯一的路由是本地路由到 VPC的 CDIR 范围
From here, we'll add another route,
从这里我们再增加一条路线
and this second route will be your default route,
第二条路线是你的默认路线
and it will point at the newly created NAT gateway
它会指向新创建的 NAT 网关